

Gonzalo, TERZANO

Web Developer
26 Years
Córdoba, Argentina
Mobile: +549 0264 154649709
E-mail: gonzaloterzano@gmail.com

PERSONAL STATEMENT

Hello! My name is Gonzalo Terzano. I am a Semi-Senior Web Developer, with 2-3 years of experience in the area. I have many skills to work as a team member and also individually. I always push myself to the limit in order to achieve excellece in my work.

EXPERIENCE

February 2016 – Present Globant Cordoba, Argentina

Position: Web UI Developer

Working in a busy team sometimes under pressure. Always making projects of eLearning, mostly using AngularJS, but also creating friendly & interactive environments with HTML5 and Phaser (JS Framework).

April 2015 – January 2016 TravelPAQ San Juan, Argentina

Position: Web UI Developer & Backend Developer

I worked in a startup focused on improve relationships between tourism companies. This was an exciting experience where I learned a lot of new and different technologies.

April 2010 – January 2016 UNSJ, FCEFyN San Juan, Argentina

Position: Teaching assistant

Worked in six different subjects, assisting in practical classes, even giving class in some particular cases.

SKILLS

✓ AngularJS

✓ JQuery

✓ JavaScript

✓ KnockoutJS

✓ HTML5

✓ CSS3

✓ Bootstrap

✓ CakePHP

✓ Git

✓ Gulp

✓ NodeJS

✓ PHP

✓ C#

✓ C

✓ SourceTree

✓ Photoshop

EDUCATION

2009 - Present

San Juan - Argentina

"Degree in Computer Science"

UNSJ Fac. Cs. Exactas F. y N.

Thesis pending GPA: 8.6 of 10

2005 - 2008

San Juan - Argentina

"Electronics Technician"

UNSJ - Esc Industrial D. F. Sarmiento

GPA: 8.57 of 10

LENGUAGES

Spanish: Native

English: Conversational level